{
  "LevelId": 5,
  "Questions": [
    {
      "id": 40,
      "level_image": 3,
      "answer_text": "PUBLIC",
      "question": "Open to everyone"
    },
    {
      "id": 41,
      "level_image": 3,
      "answer_text": "LAUNCH",
      "question": "Beginning of a mission"
    },
    {
      "id": 42,
      "level_image": 3,
      "answer_text": "ACTION",
      "question": "Doing something or taking part in an event"
    },
    {
      "id": 43,
      "level_image": 3,
      "answer_text": "TATTOO",
      "question": "Permanent body art"
    },
    {
      "id": 44,
      "level_image": 3,
      "answer_text": "CHEESE",
      "question": "Dairy product often used in sandwiches"
    },
    {
      "id": 45,
      "level_image": 3,
      "answer_text": "BARBER",
      "question": "Who specializes in cutting and styling hair"
    },
    {
      "id": 46,
      "level_image": 4,
      "answer_text": "COFFEE",
      "question": "popular beverage made from roasted beans"
    },
    {
      "id": 47,
      "level_image": 4,
      "answer_text": "PARLOR",
      "question": "Where might you go for beauty treatments"
    },
    {
      "id": 48,
      "level_image": 4,
      "answer_text": "CANYON",
      "question": "Deep gorge or ravine"
    },
    {
      "id": 49,
      "level_image": 0,
      "answer_text": "BUTTERFLY",
      "question": "Colorful winged insect"
    }
  ]
}